Guide to the Elisabeth Lloyd Papers, 1954-2017 ASP.2016.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Correspondence, 1980 - 2014; I.
  - Personal, 1983 - 2005; 2.
    - Merritt, Mr. and Mrs. Stanley, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Mirochnik, Elijah, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Mladenović, Bojana (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Mojica, Melissa, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Newman, Laurie, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Otto, Sally, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Perin, Casey, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Perry, John, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Rose, Hilary, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Roy, Ina, 1992-1995 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Sally (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Saltsman, Wayne, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Schenden, Haline, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Schiffer, Lisa (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Searle, John and Dagmar, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Slepian, Jan, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Spath, Susan, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Students (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Suarez, Mauricio, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Tawil, Nathan, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Unknown Senders (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - van Fraassen, Bas, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Wang (Wong?), Frances (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Waters, Lindsay, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Zuk, Marlene, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - University and Administrative, 1988 - 2010; 3.
    - Addison, J.W., 1997 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Bonner, Jose, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Brand, Myles, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Broughton, Janet, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Brown, Mary Ellen, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Chiara, Charles, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - COAS Policy Committee - Indiana University, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Daniels, Susan, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Freshman Learning Project - Indiana University, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Freund, Deborah A., 1998 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Gale, George, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Gieryn, Thomas, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Gilbert, Ann M., 1997 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Glenn, Evelyn - Women's Studies Dept. At Berkeley, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Greenberg, Anna and Mansbridge, Jane - Harvard University, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Hanks, Peter and Ellis, Jonathan, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Hanson, Karen, 2000-2003 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Harrington, Leo - Group in Logic and the Methodology of Science, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Holder, Martha, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Human Subjects Risk Compliance, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Kirk, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Koertge, Noretta, 1988-2000 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Lloyd, Lisa, 1997-2004 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Minsuk, Sharon, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Morse, Geoff, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Nasca, Rachel, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Nelson, Reed Alvin, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Office of the Dean at Indiana University, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Office of the President of Indiana University, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Oliver, Robert M., 1993 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Pettay, Ellen, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Plummer, Laura, 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Powell, Patricia, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Raff, Beth, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Rauch, Jennifer, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Robert, Ellen, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Smith, David H., 2000 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Smith, Linda, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Steen, Tomoko Y., 1998 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Stroup, Donna Jean, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Summers, Linda, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Wimbush, James, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Women Faculty Luncheons (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Wood, Rebecca J., 1998-2006 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Zaret, David, 2000-2003 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence with Manuscripts, 1986 - 2013; 4.
    The letters in this section were associated with manuscripts that have been annotated by Elizabeh Lloyd and/or others. The letters here are from people who may appear in other sections of the correspondence. Correspondents iin this section nclude Motoo Kimura, Phiip Kitcher, Lynn Margulies, and Michael Ruse,
    - Boucher, Doug (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Dawkins, Richard, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Dietrich, Michael, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Dupre, John, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Feldman, Marc, 1989-1995 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Fehrenbacher, Micah - The University of Chicago Press, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Harnad, Stevan, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Harvard University Press Final Ref Reports for Keywords in Evolutionary Biology, 1988-1991 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Horan, Barbara, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Keller, Margaret, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Kitcher, Phillip, 1989-1991 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Kimura, Motoo, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Margulis, Lynn, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Masters, Judith and Hamish Spencer - Sexual Selection, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Roush, Sherri (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Ruse, Michael - Contribution to Keywords in Evolutionary Biology - Correspondence with Others About Contribution, 1988-1990 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Sloep, Peter B., 1986 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Smocovitis, Betty, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Stevens, P.F., 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Uyenoyama, Marcy and Marc Feldman, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Variety of Evidence Revisited Persi Diaconis, Elisabeth Lloyd, and Brian Skyrms, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Manuscripts, 1980 - 2015; II.
  The Manuscripts series is divided into two sub-series; mauscripts authored by Elizabeth Lloyd and those written by others and sent to her for review. The manuscrips sent by others are usually annotated by Lloyd. The manuscripts cover a wide array of topics.
  - Lloyd Manuscripts, 1980 - 2015; 1.
    These manuscripts are the earlier stages of professional articles in philosophy and history of science written by Elizabeth Lloyd. There are manuscripts for Evolutionary Pscychology, Feminism as Method, Objectivity Old and New, and the Case of The Female Orgasm among others.
    - Thinking About Models in Evolutionary Theory, Philosophica, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Allometry of Individuality and Adaptation Across Levels of Selection: How Shall We Name and Generalize the Unit of Darwinism Elisabeth Lloyd and Stephen Jay Gould, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Beyond Variability: Models of Selection In and Out of Biology Elisabeth Lloyd, Marcus Feldman, and Ben Kerr (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Chapter 7 Bias (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Constitutional Failures of Meritocracy and Their Consequences (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Evolutionary Psychology: The Burdens of Proof (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Feminism as Method: What Scientists Get That Philosophers Don't, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - How To Do The Best Biology Review of R. Lewontin's "The Triple Helix", 2000 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Is Female Orgasm as Adaptation? Evolutionary Explanations of Human Female Orgasms (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Model Robustness as a Confirmatory Virtue: Variety of Evidence and Climate Science, 2014 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Objectivity: A Framework, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Objectivity: Old and New (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Objectivity and a Comparison of Methodological Scenario Approaches for Climate Change Research Elisabeth A. Lloyd and Vanessa J. Schweizer, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Orgasm Occurence Across Sexual Orientations in a Probability Sample of U.S. Singles Justin R. Garcia, Kim Wallen, Elisabeth A. Lloyd, Helen Fisher (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Perspectives on 'Recent Scientific Approaches to the Mind/Body Problem', 1980 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - PGS Manuscript (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Pluralism Without Genic Causes? Lisa Lloyd et al., 2005 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Robustness and Variety of Evidence: Observational Support for Models (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Rumors About Selection Final/Last Version Elisabeth Lloyd, Richard Lewontin, and Marcus Feldman, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Rumors About Selection Working Drafts pt. 1 Lloyd, Lewontin, and Feldman (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Rumors About Selection Working Drafts pt. 2 Lloyd, Lewontin, and Feldman (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Rx: Distinguish Group Selection from Group Adaptation (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Sex Differences in Partnered Orgasm Experience Among U.S. Singles (Tentative Title) Justin R. Garcia, Kim Wallen, Elisabeth A. Lloyd, and Helen E. Fisher (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Sex Differences in Partnered Orgasm Experience Across Age, Sexual Orientation, and Relationship Status (Tentative Title) Justin R. Garcia, Kim Wallen, Elisabeth A. Lloyd, and Helen E. Fisher*** (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Species Selection on Variability Elisabeth Lloyd and Stephen Jay Gould, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Structure and Confirmation of Evolutionary Theory (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - The Anatomy of Objectivity: Its Uses and Abuses in Philosophy and Science, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - The Case of the Female Orgasm Manuscript Changes, August 2004 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - The Case of the Female Orgasm Proof, August 2004 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - The Case of the Female Orgasm Corrected Page Proofs, November 2004 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - The Case of the Female Orgasm Corrections, November 2004 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - The Case of the Female Orgasm Final Manuscript, November 2004 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - The Case of the Female Orgasm, November 2004 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - The Case of the Female Orgasm Sticky Note Corrections, November 2004 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - The Case of the Female Orgasm Uncorrected Page Proofs, November 2004 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - The Multiple Orgasm Gaps: Differences in Orgasm Frequency Between Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, and Heterosexual Men and Women in a U.S. National Sample David A. Frederick, H. Kate St. John, Justin R. Garcia, and Elisabeth A. Lloyd, 2015 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - The Structure and Confirmation of Evolutionary Theory Bas van Fraassen marked draft, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Variety of Evidence for Climate Change Plus Notes, 1991-2006 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Variety of Evidence Draft (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Violence Against Science: Rape and Evolution (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Why the Gene Will Not Return, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Manuscripts Sent By Others, 1988 - 2013; 2.
    These are manuscripts sent by others for review and commentary by Lloyd.. Manuscripts from Peter Godfrey-Smith, james Greisemer, Michael Ruse, James Valentine, and Bas Van Fraasen among others are in this section.
    - Ahouse, Jeremy C., 1999 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Anderson, Carl G., 1997 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Anderson, Elizabeth, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Boivin, Jacky from Symons, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Brouwer, Christien, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Browne, Kingsley R., 1995 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Burian, Richard M. (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Burt, D. Brent, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Capshew, James H. et al., 2003 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Carson, Ronald (sent by "OB") (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Chiara, Charles et al., 1992 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Collier, John, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Daston, Lorraine, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Dorling, John from Dick Jeffrey, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Downes, Steve, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Dupre, John (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Exaptation, Adaptation, and Evolutionary Psychology (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Friedman, Marilyn, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Frisch, Matthias (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Fujimura, Joan H., 1991 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Glidden, David from Eric Schwitzgebel, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Godfrey-Smith, Peter et al., 2001 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Goss, ?, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Griesemer, James, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Haslanger, Sally, 1991-1997 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Haufe, Chris, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Kempton, Kimberly, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Kraus, Cynthia, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Laubichler, Manfred, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Levels, Time and Fitness in Evolutionary Transitions in Individuality Unknown Author, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Lidicker, William, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 5a)
    - Linn, Marcia C., 1989 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Lloyd, James B., 1992 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Lowe, John B. and Mazaudon, Martine, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Maasen, Sabine (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Manning, Richard, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Martinot, Steve (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Masters, Judith C. from Dick Rayner, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - McShea, Dan, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Mol, Annemarie, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Moss, Lenny, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Mylott, Anne, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Paracer, Surindar (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Reiser, Hans (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Rouse, Joseph (pt. 1) (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Rouse, Joseph (pt. 2) (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Ruse, Michael, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Schaffner, Kenneth, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Siefkes, Dirk, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Strohman, Richard, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Unlabeled Manuscripts (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Valentine, Jim (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - van Fraassen, Bas (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Winther, Rasmus (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Wylie, Alison, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Composition - Working Notes, 1978 - 2014; III.
  This series contains materials that record early stages of research and writing for both articles and books directed to a professional audience, and to other articles on topics of interest to Lloyd but perhaps not exclusively for an audience of working philosophers and biologists.
  - Handwritten Notes by Lloyd, 1983 - 2014; 1.
    - Adaptation Notes, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Additivity notes, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Aristotelian Society Response to Wendy Parker, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Arnold, Stevan J., 1983 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - BAPS, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Boorman and Levitt, Genetics of Altruism, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Canada TV The Nature of Things Kym Dopheide, 2013 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Carnap, Rudolf, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - CIB - Objectivity Synthese, 2013 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Chatterjee, Ansu, 2014 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Cranor, Carl, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Dugatkin and Reeve (1994), 2004 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Explanation/Confirmation Chapter Notes, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Feldman, Marc, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Fine, Arthur - Stanford, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Fixation of Belief/Ideas Clear/Doctrine of Chances, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - G. Markus, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Garcia, Justin and Peter B. Gray, 2012 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Genes R Us: Session 1, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Hacking, Ian, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Harwood, Jon, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - HPS Stats on Climate Science - Hockey Stick Case, 2013 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Hull, David, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Kanzi Paper RCL Comments, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Kerr, Benjamin and Peter Godfrey-Smith, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - King and Belsky (2012), 2013 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Longino, Helen - Book, 2011 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Mann, Michael CL Book, 2011 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Mathias Frisch - Bas van Fraassen on Simpson's Paradox and IBE, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Matthen and Ariew - Philosophy of Science - Selection and Causation, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - McDowell, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Overland, Jim and Climate Data Arctic, 2013 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Perin, Casey, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - JRG Replicators, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Schweizer, Vanessa, 2014 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Sluga, Hans, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Sober, Elliott, 2012 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Taylor, Peter, 2011 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Trivers, Robert and Hope Hare, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - van Fraassen, Bas, 1987-1996 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Miscellaneous Notes Many Undated, 1978 - 2004; 2.
    - Adaptationism (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Alexander, Richard D., 1989 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Allelic ≠ Haploid Model (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Autonomous Models (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Baker, RR et al. (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Bias of Androcentrism (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Brody, B.A. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Can We Reconcile Physicalism and Anti-Reductionism in the Philosophy of Biology? (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Chapter 1 notes (not used) (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Chapter 2 notes (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Chapter 3 of Org. Evoly. Accts. Pre 1987 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Computer Notes (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Correction to Barash Online (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Cranor, Carl (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Daly, M. et al., 1978 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Evolutionary Ethics (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Feldman, Marc (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Foreplay Notes (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Fristrup, Kurt (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Glymour, Bruce, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Gould, Stephen Jay and Elisabeth Lloyd (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Griesemer, James R. (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Hartl, D. Principles of Population Genetics, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Higher Level Selection (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Hrdy, Sarah et al. (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Hume Script (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Independent Testing and Variety of Evidence Notes (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Jonty Rougier (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Kitcher, Philip et al., 1990 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Kinsey Methods (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Lewontin, Richard, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Margot - Darwin Paper - Variety of fit points (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - McCarthy, Timothy (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - McCright, Aaron and Riley, Dunlop, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - MET notes (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Miscellaneous Notes (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Miscellaneous "To-Do" Items (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Nelkin, Dorothy et al., 1989 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Okasha, Samir (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Philosophy and Education (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Procreative Focus (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Reznick, David et al., 1996 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Shanahan, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Short, R.V., 1980 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Species Selection notes (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Stanford, Kyle, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Stephens, Chris, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Sterelny, Kim and Philip Kitcher, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Symons, Donald, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Synthese Ref. Rep. Epistemology of Climate Model Assessment (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Thornhill et al. (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Uterine Suction (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Walsh, D.M. et al. (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Wasser, S.K. et al. (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Waters, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - What Philosophers Need to Know (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Williams, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Commentary by Others, 1982 - 2013; 3.
    - Allen, Colin, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Baker, Jason M., 2006 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Burian, Richard, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Darden, Lindley - A Semantic Approach to the Structure of Population Genetics and Selection Models and the Darwinian Theory of Natural Selection, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Dunn, Matt, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Fagan, Melinda, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Griesemer, James, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Lewontin, Richard, 2005-2006 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Lively, Curt, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Millstein, Roberta, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous commentary on Confirmation of Ecological and Evolutionary Models paper, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous commentary on "SCET" paper, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Morrison, Monica, 2013 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Odenbaugh, Jay, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Okasha, Samir (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Published Reviews of Lloyd's Books, 1989-1994 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Sober, Elliott, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Waters, C. Kenneth, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Weisberg, Michael, 2004-2006 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Winther, Rasmus, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Writing Process, 1982 - 2014; 4.
    - A Semantic Approach to the Structure of Modern Evolutionary Theory, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - A Semantic Approach to the Structure of Population Genetics manuscript, referee reports, notes, and submission to 'Philosophy of Science', 1983 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Confirmation paper notes, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Explanation Notes, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Talk with Stephen Jay Gould, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Talk with E. O. Wilson, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Talk with Richard Lewontin, 1984-1987 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Interrelations of Models, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Mathematical Models and the Structure of Evolutionary Theory Bas van Fraassen comments, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - The Confirmation of Kin Selection: A Close Look at Trivers and Hare, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Mathematical Models and the Structure of Evolutionary Theory-Salzburg-Final, 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Confirmation of Ecological and Evolutionary Models, 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Confirmation of Ecological and Evolutionary Models revisions and correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - "Units" comments from Richard Burian, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - "Units" rough draft with notes and Bas van Fraassen comments, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - "Units" comments from Bill Wimsatt, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Confirmation of Ecological and Evolutionary Models proof, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Empirical Evaluation of Units of Selection Controversies miscellaneous papers, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Evaluation of Evidence in Units of Selection Controversies, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Evaluation of Evidence in Group Selection Debates, Philosophy of Science Association paper, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Is Female Orgasm an Adaptation? Evolutionary Explanations of Human Female Orgasm First draft, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Mathematical Models and the Structure of Evolutionary Theory Salzburg page proofs and correspondence, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Notes and Comments on "Units", 1986 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Thinking About Models in Evolutionary Theory, January Philosophica, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Paper with Steve Gould notes, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - A Structural Approach to Defining Units of Selection revised versions and correspondence, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Response to Sloep and Van der Steen proof, notes, and correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Keywords in Evolutionary Biology correspondence, notes, miscellaneous, 1987-1989 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Keywords in Evolutionary Biology Early Project Draft, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Keywords in Evolutionary Biology permissions, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Cosmides Working File, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Keywords in Evolutionary Biology correspondence and notes cont'd., 1989-1991 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Keywords in Evolutionary Biology Correspondence, Notes, and Manuscripts, 1990-1992 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Kathryn comments on The Secret Life of Objectivity, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Secret Life of Objectivity Drafts, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Ideas for Future Papers, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - All About Eve: Biases in Evolutionary Explanations of Women's Sexuality, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Philosophy of Science Association Symposium: Feyerabend, Mill, and Pluralism Paper and Correspondence, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - The Anatomy of Objectivity: Its Uses and Abuses in Philosophy and Science, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Objectivity: A Framework manuscript with edits, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Refs to Get, 1997-2001 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Bibliography and Citations for The Case of the Female Orgasm, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Melinda Comments, June 2004 (Box 22, Folder 10)